travelandtourworld.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Travelandtourworld.comTravelandtourworld.com

**Travel And Tour World, Privacy Policy**

  Travel And Tour World’s main intent to publish this Internet Privacy Policy is to inform you of our practices regarding the use of information you provide us through communicating with Travel and Tour World. This policy is not applicable to information gathered by other methods or controlled by other agreements.

  **Information Collection: How We Collect**

  The information collected by Travel and Tour World involves several methodologies including registration with Travel and Tour World on this website, subscribing to Travel and Tour World’s services through this website, using Travel and Tour World’s products or services via the website, and when you visit the websites of certain Travel and Tour World and its related partners,

_User Registration_

By registering on our website, we ask for and collect your information through your name, email address, zip code, industry, address, etc. Once you register with Travel and Tour World and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

  _Newsletters_  
Information are also collected from Travel and Tour World’s newsletter services. Users can sign in to daily newsletter or can apply for exclusive e-blasts. The information is collected through such service.

  _Contests_  
Users can choose to participate in promotional contests conducted by Travel and Tour World. The information is then collected through personal information which is required at the time of registration.

  _Events and Programs_  
Users may elect to participate in events that Travel and Tour World conducts from time to time. Travel and Tour World collects personal information in connection with user registration for and participation.

  _Cookies_  
By definition “Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Travel and Tour World or its advertisers may send a cookie to your computer through your browser. Travel and Tour World uses cookies in order to track page requests and the duration of each user’s visit. The use of cookies allows us to provide a user’s browser with information tailored to the visitor’s preferences. Users can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of their browser. Users can either reset their browser to refuse all cookies or allow their browser to show them when a cookie is being sent. Not accepting the cookies may diminish your experience at our website.

  _IP Addresses_  
Travel and Tour World automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser. The information includes your IP address, TTW cookie information, and the website page you request. The information is used to fix problems with our server and to review the website aggregate. The collected information may be used to improve our web page content.

  _Through Purchases_  
Purchasing something from Travel and Tour World’s website entails identity validation. We need to collect information like your name, email address, mailing address, credit card number, etc. This will help us to carry out and deliver your order in a streamlined way. Credit card information will not be shared or sold to unaffiliated third parties for any purpose without your express permission, except as necessary to process the transaction.

  **Use of Information**  
The basic idea to collect your personal information is to deliver the service you requested. Travel and Tour World may use personal information in a variety of ways including the following:

Travel and Tour World may use personal information through its website to send out targeted email promotions on behalf of its advertisers and industry partners.

Travel and Tour World may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies in order to better deliver products and services that may benefit you.

Travel and Tour World may use personal information to contact users in order to renew subscriptions

Travel and Tour World may use personally identifiable information to send notification of TTW’s or our partners’ products and services by such methods as email and/or postal mail.

All financial information of yours’ will be used to validate your credit card and collect payments for your purchases, orders, subscriptions, etc.

Travel and Tour World may send product announcements or special edition newsletters to online registrants.

If you participate in a Travel and Tour World event, we may contact you to provide additional information concerning these programs.

Travel and Tour World conducts user surveys to better target our content to our audiences. The consolidated information collected is sometimes shared with our advertisers; however, we will do not share specific individual information with a third-party.

Travel and Tour World also operates several websites featuring its travel-related content and services. We may share personal information collected from users of its websites internally across these websites to better serve its users.

Travel and Tour World has an array of products and services. In order to promote such, Travel and Tour World allows users to choose specific lists of products that interests them the most. All email promotions sent from TTW provide an opt-out link at the bottom of the email pursuant to which users can opt-out of specific products and promotions. If you receive one of these emails and wish to unsubscribe please follow the instructions given in each email or contact [technical@travelandtourworld.com](mailto:technical@travelandtourworld.com) or [editor@travelandtourworld.com](mailto:editor@travelandtourworld.com)

  **Sharing of Information Collected With Third Parties**  
In general, Travel and Tour World does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies or third parties except to provide products or services you have requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: :

We may provide personal information about our users to trusted partners and vendors who work on behalf of or with Travel and Tour World under confidentiality and similar agreements prohibiting such parties’ further use of the information. These companies may use your personal information to help TTW communicate with you about offers from TTW and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to use or share this information

When you register a third party sponsored event, contest, or other promotion, the third party will be provided personally identifiable information

Travel and Tour World may share personal information such as email addresses with trusted third parties who deliver content that is likely to be of interest to the user and subject to opt-out obligation on the part of such third party.

We may share personal information where we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served on TTW, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

We may share such information where we have a good faith belief that it is necessary in order to investigate (or assist in the investigation of), prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of TTW’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

If TTW is acquired by or merged with another company, we will transfer information about you to this other company in connection with the acquisition or merger.

**Security**  
This website takes commercially reasonable precautions to protect your personal information. When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as credit card and payment information, we re-direct users to industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encrypted servers. As a result, sensitive data you submit to our website such as credit card and payment information is transmitted securely over the Internet.

  **Security**  
This website takes commercially reasonable precautions to protect your personal information. When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as credit card and payment information, we re-direct users to industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encrypted servers. As a result, sensitive data you submit to our website such as credit card and payment information is transmitted securely over the Internet.

  **Disclaimers**  
Travel and Tour World is not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. TTW also links to a wide variety of other sites and contains advertisements of third parties. Privacy Policies of third parties does not fall under the purview of Travel and Tour World.

  **About Children’s Privacy**  
This TTW website is not intended for use by children and TTW does not knowingly collect information from children. You must be 18 years old to access or use this site.

  **Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Travel and Tour World reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on the website. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon positing on the website. Users will be informed of changes to this Privacy Policy via the “updated as of” link on the TTW website.

  **What Else Should I Know About My Privacy When Online?**  
Travel and Tour World website contains many hyperlinks to related websites. The Our website also contains advertisements of third parties. This is to notify that Travel and Tour World is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party websites or advertisers. TTW does not share any of the individual personal information you provide TTW with the websites to which TTW links, except as stated elsewhere within this Privacy Policy, although TTW may share aggregate data with such websites (such as how many people use our Site).

  Check third party websites to know their Privacy Policies. When Travel and Tour World embeds third party content into one of it’s Travel and Tour World web pages, we will use considerable efforts to advise our users that they have logged out of TTW operated website and are entering a third party controlled website.  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

  Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you’re online.

**Your Consent To This Policy**  
By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information by Travel and Tour World as specified in this policy. Please also note that your use of the website is governed by the Travel and Tour World Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy or the Terms and Conditions, please do not use the website, products and/or services.

To update your email address or change your email preferences please contact [technical@travelandtourworld.com](mailto:technical@travelandtourworld.com) or [editor@travelandtourworld.com](mailto:editor@travelandtourworld.com)
